cottonbabies.com 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy – Cotton Babies

**Cotton Babies Privacy Policy**

Cotton Babies, Inc. (“Cotton Babies”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes Cotton Babies’ practices in connection with the information that we collect through our websites or mobile applications owned and controlled by Cotton Babies as well as offline where notice is legally required. By providing personal and other information to Cotton Babies, you agree to this Privacy Policy.

**Collection of Your Personal Information**

At some Cotton Babies sites, when you create an account we ask you to provide personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, or telephone number. If you choose to make a purchase, we will ask for additional information, such as your credit card number and billing address, which is used to process your order. In order to access some Cotton Babies services, you will be asked to sign in with an e-mail address and password. By signing in on one Cotton Babies’ site or service, you may be automatically signed into other Cotton Babies’ sites and services. We may collect information about your interaction with Cotton Babies’ sites and services. For example, we may use Web site analytics tools on our site to retrieve information from your browser, including the site you came from, the search engine(s) and the keywords you used to find our site, the pages you view within our site, your browser add-ons, and your browser’s width and height.

We may also use technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take on our sites and services. Additionally, we collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times, and referring Web site addresses. We also may deliver advertisements and utilize Web site analytics tools (see the Display of Advertising section below).

When you receive newsletters or promotional e-mail from Cotton Babies, we may use customized links, or similar technologies to determine whether the e-mail has been opened and which links you click in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or other information.

In order to offer you a more consistent and personalized experience in your interactions with Cotton Babies, information collected through one Cotton Babies service may be combined with information obtained through other Cotton Babies services. We may also supplement the information we collect with information obtained from other companies. For example, we may use services from other companies that enable us to derive a general geographic area based on your IP address in order to customize certain services to your geographic area.

From time to time, we may also ask you to consider participating in marketing surveys to help us improve our sites, services, and products. If you choose to participate in our surveys, you will be asked to provide general demographic information or feedback. Your participation in our surveys is always voluntary. If you do not wish to share your demographic information or feedback with us, you do not have to. If you do participate, we may use your responses, together with other responses we receive, to evaluate and improve our sites, services, and products. We will never publicly disclose your survey responses in a manner that will divulge your personal information or link your responses to you.

**Use of Your Personal Information**

Cotton Babies collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its sites and services and to improve your user experience. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the sites or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services, and technologies; and displaying content and advertising that are customized to your interests and preferences. For more information about the use of information for advertising, see the Display of Advertising section below.

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, order-related communications, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. Some Cotton Babies services may send periodic correspondence that is considered part of the service. Additionally, with your permission, we may send you information about other Cotton Babies products and services.

**Sharing of Your Personal Information**

Except as described in this policy, we will not disclose your personal information outside of Cotton Babies and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your consent. See the Communication Preferences section below for more information.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, hosting websites, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services and use of our websites and services by you and other users. Those service providers will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose. However, some of our third-party vendors may use anonymized aggregate data to improve their services. For example, with regard to credit card processing services, our fraud detection vendors may use aggregate data to help them more accurately detect fraudulent uses of credit cards. We may access or disclose information about you, including the content of your communications, in order to: (a) comply with the law or respond to lawful requests or legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of Cotton Babies or our customers, including the enforcement of our agreements or policies governing your use of the services; or (c) act on a good faith belief that such access or disclosure is necessary to protect the personal safety of Cotton Babies’ employees, customers, or the public. We may also disclose personal information as part of a corporate transaction such as a merger or sale of assets.

**Research & Statistical Analysis**

We may, from time to time, use your personal or other information to perform research and statistical analysis to help us evaluate and improve our sites, services, and product offerings. Cotton Babies may perform such research and analysis itself or may use third-party vendors and services, such as Google Analytics. As of the date of this Privacy Policy, Cotton Babies has implemented Google Analytics’ Demographics and Interests Advertising Features. For more information about how your information may be used in connection with our implementation of Google Analytics (including information on how you may opt-out of sharing your information or control how your information is shared), please visit <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>.

For additional information on opting-out of sharing your information and on protecting your information and safety online, generally, you may choose to visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s “Consumer Opt-Out” page (<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>) and Google’s “Safety Center” (https://www.google.com/safetycenter/).

Cotton Babies has also implemented Google AdWords conversion tracking to gather anonymous data (i.e., information that does not contain your personal information) to help us better analyze the effectiveness of our marketing efforts and to help us learn how to better reach our customers. Google AdWords conversion tracking uses a pixel tag (a tiny graphic image) placed on our site that can track activity on the site and can be used to measure the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. These pixel tags may be used in conjunction with cookies. Also, when you purchase items on our sites, anonymous sales conversion information (that does not contain your personal information) may be transmitted to Google Analytics using javascript. To learn more about conversion tracking, please visit <https://support.google.com/adwords/answer/1722022?hl=en>.

**Accessing Your Personal Information**

You might have the ability to view or edit your personal information online. In order to help prevent your personal information from being viewed by others, you will be required to sign in with your credentials (e-mail address and password). You can access and update your information by logging into your account and clicking on the “My Account” page. Some Cotton Babies sites or services may collect personal information that is not accessible via the “My Account” page. However, in such cases, you may be able to access that information through alternative means of access described by the service. Or, you may also contact us by phone at 1.888.33.BABIES (1.888.332.2243) (Monday through Friday, 9 a.m. CT - 5 p.m. CT) or by e-mail at [contactus@cottonbabies.com](mailto:contactus@cottonbabies.com).

**Communication Preferences**

You can stop the delivery of future promotional materials from Cotton Babies sites and services by following the specific instructions in the materials you receive (e.g., by clicking the “Unsubscribe” or “Safe Unsubscribe” links at the bottom of the bottom of the message) or by contacting us via e-mail at [contactus@cottonbabies.com](mailto:contactus@cottonbabies.com).

This choice does not apply to the display of online advertising. Nor does it apply to the receipt of mandatory service communications that are considered part of certain Cotton Babies services, which you may receive periodically unless you cancel the service.

**Display of Advertising**

Many of the Web sites and online services we offer, as well as those of our partners, are supported by advertising. We may display ads on our own sites and on the sites of our advertising partners.

When we display online advertisements to you, we will place one or more persistent cookies on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time we display an ad to you. The cookies we use for advertising have an expiry date of no more than 2 years. Because we may serve advertisements on many different Web sites, we are able to compile information over time about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements we display. We may use this information to make predictions about your characteristics, interests, or preferences and to display targeted advertisements that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also associate this information with your subsequent visit, purchase, or other activity on participating advertisers’ Web sites in order to determine the effectiveness of the advertisements.

Although the majority of the online advertisements on Cotton Babies sites are displayed by Cotton Babies, we also allow third-party ad serving companies, including other ad networks, to display advertisements on our sites. We use Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise Cotton Babies across the Internet. Google AdWords Remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the Cotton Babies website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. This cookie does not identify you or give access to your computer. The cookie is used to say "This person visited a particular page on this web site, so show them ads relating to that page." Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you. If you do not wish to participate in our use of Google AdWords Remarketing, you can opt out by visiting [Google Ad Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated). You can also opt out of third-party vendors’ use of cookies by visiting [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

**Security of Your Personal Information**

Cotton Babies is committed to protecting the security of your personal information and information collected for advertising purposes. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number or password) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. Likewise, any of our third-party vendors with access to your information are required to take similar steps to protect the security of your information. Nevertheless, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic data storage is 100% secure. Consequently, while Cotton Babies strives to use commercially reasonable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We remind you always to exercise discretion when you share information over the Internet.

If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

**Collection and Use of Children’s Personal Information**

Cotton Babies is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities. Cotton Babies does not target its Web sites or mobile applications to children less than thirteen (13) years of age or knowingly collect information from such children for the purpose of selling products or services. Cotton Babies may participate in select programs in support of schools and communities. If you believe we may have received personal information from your child, please contact us immediately.

**Use of Cookies**

Cotton Babies Web sites use “cookies” to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content and appropriate advertising on your later visits to these sites. Cotton Babies Web sites also use cookies as described in the Collection of your Information and Display of Advertising sections of this privacy policy.

When you sign in to a site using your Cotton Babies log-in credentials, we store your unique ID number, and the time you signed in, in an encrypted cookie on your hard disk. This cookie allows you to move from page to page at the site without having to sign in again on each page. When you sign out, these cookies are deleted from your computer. We also use cookies to improve the sign in experience. For example, your e-mail address may be stored in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you sign out. This cookie allows your e-mail address to be pre-populated, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. If you are using a public computer or do not otherwise want this information to be stored, you can select the appropriate radio button on the sign-in page, and this cookie will not be used.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of Cotton Babies sites and services that depend on cookies, and some advertising preferences that are dependent on cookies may not be able to be respected.

**Controlling Unsolicited** **E-mail** **(“Spam”)**

Cotton Babies is concerned about controlling unsolicited commercial e-mail, or “spam.” Cotton Babies will not sell, lease or rent its e-mail subscriber lists to third parties. While Cotton Babies continues to actively review and implement new technology, such as expanded filtering features, there is no currently available technology that will totally prevent the sending and receiving of unsolicited e-mail. Using junk e-mail tools and being cautious about the sharing of your e-mail address while online will help reduce the amount of unsolicited e-mail you receive.

**Links to Other Websites**

Cotton Babies’ sites and services may contain links to other websites or services that are not owned or controlled by Cotton Babies. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy policies or terms of use for such third-party websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our sites and to read the applicable privacy policies and terms of use for any third-party websites you may visit or services you may use.

**International Visitors to Our Site**

Cotton Babies’ sites are hosted in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States please be aware that the laws in your location governing the collection and use of your personal information may differ from U.S. law. If you do share your personal information with us, please note that you are voluntarily transferring your information to the United States, that you consent to that transfer, that you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, and that you agree to waive, to the fullest extent permitted by law, any other rights or protections you may have under the laws of your location or any other jurisdiction outside of the United States.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We encourage you to periodically review this policy to be informed of how Cotton Babies is protecting your information.

**Enforcement of This Privacy Policy**

If you have questions regarding this policy, you should contact us by using the information below.

**Contacting Us**

Cotton Babies welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have questions about this policy, please contact us by phone at 1.888.33.BABIES (1.888.332.2243) (Monday through Friday, 9 a.m. CT - 5 p.m. CT) or by e-mail at [contactus@cottonbabies.com](mailto:contactus@cottonbabies.com).

Cotton Babies Privacy, Cotton Babies, Inc., 1299 N. Highway Dr, Fenton, MO 63026

© 2012-2017 Cotton Babies, Inc. All rights reserved.
